[Music]
when you work with multiple companies
and multiple environments in business
Central it can be useful to have a
visual identification of which company
you're working in in which environment
you have the environment and Company
selector in the top
menu here you can see all your
companies here I have assigned company
badges to each of the companies in my
portfolio I have four environments in
this case and in some environments I
have multiple companies and I like the
visual identification to have let's say
a yellow and red and green and orange
badge to help me identify quickly am I
in the US environment or the Danish
environment and so on depending on your
structure you may want to choose
different colors notice that I can also
set different texts on these company
badges the shape of the company badge
signifies the type of environment round
company badges signify produ C
environments Square company badges
signify sandbox environments so where do
we set up these company badges we do
that at the company information page you
hit the C wheel the settings wheel and
you go to company
information scroll down until you find
the company bad section here you can
determine how the company badge you look
in terms of should it be a custom one
what is the style and in terms of color
and what is the text you can enter up to
six characters in the company badge
using company badges is a great way to
help you quickly identify which company
you're working
in thank you for watching
[Music]